- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Where's that order
for table three?
- 订单在哪里
对于表三？
Table five's
ready to be bussed!
表五
准备好乘坐巴士了！
There's a spill in
the bathroom!
里面有溢出物
浴室！
I need ya swabbing the decks,
Mr. Squidward!
我需要你擦拭甲板，
章鱼哥先生！
Hmm?
SpongeBob!
唔？
海绵宝宝！
Table eight needs more
coral fries!
表八需要更多
珊瑚薯条！
Hop to it, boy!
跳起来吧，孩子！
- [panting]
Hopping, sir!
- [气喘吁吁]
跳跃吧，先生！
- My thirst is
not yet quenched!
- 我的口渴是
还没有熄灭！
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Ha!
[grunts]
- 哈！
[咕哝]
Here you go!
Thank you!
干得好！
谢谢你！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
No free refills!
Ha!
没有免费补充！
哈!
- [grunts]
I'm out of ketchup!
- [咕哝]
我的番茄酱用完了！
- We need utensils!
- [moaning]
- 我们需要餐具！
- [呻吟]
[car horn honks]
- I ordered this to go!
[汽车喇叭鸣响]
- 我命令这个走！
- [grunts]
Whoo-hoo!
- [咕哝]
呼呼！
Oh, ho!
哦，嗬！
all: Arrgh!
全体：啊啊！
- Hey!
Ah, ha-ha!
- 嘿！
啊哈哈！
You won't be pilferin'
你不会偷窃
me precious profits today,
pirates!
今天我获得了宝贵的利润，
海盗！
[all grunt]
[全都咕哝]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Aww.
- 哇。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- [babbles]
- [胡言乱语]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[all groaning]
[全都呻吟]
Phew!
唷！
Yep, takes a pretty steady claw
to oversee this ship.
是的，需要一个相当稳定的爪子
来监督这艘船。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[barks, sniffs]
[吠叫，嗅嗅]
What is it, girl?
What do you smell?
这是什么，女孩？
你闻到什么味道了？
Whoa!
[claw barks]
哇！
[爪声]
- Ooh!
- 哦！
Find a penny.
Pick it up.
找一分钱。
捡起来。
All day long
you'll have a penny!
一整天
你会得到一分钱！
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
What a good girl!
多么好的一个女孩啊！
- Order up!
- 订购吧！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[yells]
[喊叫]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Hey, a penny!
- 嘿，一分钱！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[siren blares]
[警笛声]
- Ah!
Somebody call an ambulance!
- 啊！
有人叫救护车吗！
Oh, you're here.
哦，你来了。
Wait, Mr. Krabs!
等等，蟹老板！
Who's in charge
while you're out?
谁负责
当你出去的时候？
- [gibberish]
- Yes?
- [胡言乱语]
- 是吗？
- [groans]
- Yes?
- [呻吟]
- 是吗？
Yeah?
Yes?
是的？
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[SpongeBob
and Squidward groan]
[海绵宝宝
和章鱼哥的呻吟]
- [weakly] Not SpongeBob.
- Let's go.
- [弱弱地] 不是海绵宝宝。
- 我们走吧。
- No! No!
- Ooh, he picked me!
- 不！不！
- 哦，他选了我！
I--I'm in charge!
我——我负责！
Don't worry, Mr. Krabs,
别担心，蟹老板，
I'll be the best boss
the Krusty Krab ever had!
我会成为最好的老板
蟹堡王曾经吃过！
Just like you, Mr. Krabs!
就像你一样，蟹老板！
- Ha!
You can't do Krabs's job!
- 哈！
你不能做蟹老板的工作！
- [sniffs]
Oh, I can't?
- [嗅嗅]
哦，我不能吗？
- Of course not!
- 当然不是！
You're going to get some
annoying idea in your head,
你会得到一些
你脑子里烦人的想法
act all silly,
and ruin everything!
表现得很愚蠢，
并毁掉一切！
Like you always do.
就像你平常做的那样。
- Well, I guess if
I wanna boss like Mr. Krabs...
- 好吧，我想如果
我想要像蟹老板那样的老板...
I'll have to think like Krabs!
我得像蟹蟹一样思考！
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- [groaning]
- [humming]
- [呻吟]
- [嗡嗡声]
- Mr. Krabs,
I'm so glad you're back!
- 蟹老板先生，
我很高兴你回来了！
Ah!
- [whines]
啊!
- [哀嚎]
- Ooh, just wait till you see
- 哦，等你看到
what I've done
to your restaurant!
我做了什么
到你的餐厅！
- [muffled cries]
- [低沉的哭声]
- Oh!
- 哦！
- Nothing!
Isn't it great?
- 没有什么！
不是很好吗？
Everything's just how
you left it!
一切都不过如此
你离开了！
Whenever we have a problem
around here, I ask myself,
每当我们遇到问题时
在这里，我问自己，
"What would Mr. Krabs do?"
And then I do that!
“蟹老板会怎么做？”
然后我就这么做了！
I even hired a new fry cook,
我什至雇了一个新的炒菜厨师
since I'm too busy being
the boss now.
因为我太忙了
现在的老板。
Just like you would have done!
就像你会做的那样！
- [muffled] No, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- [低声] 不，不！
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
- Hmm, hmm, hmm.
- 嗯，嗯，嗯。
- Don't worry, I taught him
everything I know!
- 别担心，我教过他
我所知道的一切！
- [babbling]
- [胡言乱语]
[laughs]
[笑]
- [hums]
- [哼哼]
- Order's up!
- 订单已到！
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
- You'll have a better view
- 你会有更好的视野
of my managerial magic
from over here.
我的管理魔法
从这里。
- I'm out of napkins!
- 我的餐巾纸用完了！
- Ooh, Here we go!
Watch me work!
- 哦，我们开始了！
看我干活！
Your napkin, sir!
先生，您的餐巾纸！
- Thank you!
- 谢谢你！
- Hey!
This table is too wobbly!
- 嘿！
这桌子也太晃了吧！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Well, let the boss
take care of that, huh?
- 好吧，让老板
照顾好这个吧？
Ta-da!
- [groans]
哒哒！
- [呻吟]
- Ooh!
Nice.
- 哦！
好的。
- [hums]
- Ahem.
- [哼哼]
- 咳咳。
- What do you want?
- 你想要什么？
- Squidward!
What would Mr. Krabs say?
- 章鱼哥！
蟹老板会说什么？
At the Krusty Krab,
Mr. Squidward,
在蟹堡王店里，
章鱼哥先生，
we're always polite
to our payin' customers!"
我们总是很有礼貌
给我们的付费客户！”
- Welcome to the Krusty Krab.
May I please take your order?
- 欢迎来到蟹堡王。
我可以接受您的订单吗？
- Remember, Squidward,
service with a smile!
- 记住，章鱼哥，
微笑服务！
Here, try one of Mr. Krabs's
vintage training devices!
来，尝尝蟹老板的一份
老式训练设备！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[moans]
[呻吟声]
May I please take your order?
我可以接受您的订单吗？
- Oh, uh,
I'll take a Krabby Patty.
- 哦，呃，
我要一份蟹肉饼。
Hold the freaky smile!
[nervous chuckle]
保持诡异的微笑！
[紧张的笑声]
- [moans]
- [呻吟]
- I think that went
pretty well, don't you?
- 我想就这样了
很好，不是吗？
[yells]
[喊叫]
- SpongeBob, you aggravating,
obnoxious, loathsome little--
- 海绵宝宝，你真烦人，
讨厌的、可恶的小——
[saw buzzing]
[看到嗡嗡声]
- Um, hold that constructive
criticism, Squidward.
- 嗯，保持建设性的态度
批评，章鱼哥。
I'll be right back!
我马上回来！
Patrick, what are you doing?
帕特里克，你在做什么？
- Huh?
I'm cleaning the deli slicer.
- 啊？
我正在清洁熟食切片机。
I used the tongs like you said.
我按照你说的用了钳子。
- Ah, ah, ah!
- 啊啊啊！
"The tongs are for
holding rags, not bricks!"
“钳子是为了
拿的是破布，不是砖头！”
Let me finish this, pal.
You get back on the grill.
让我完成这个，朋友。
你回到烤架上。
- Okeydoke.
- [yells]
- 奥基多克。
- [大喊]
- What the...
- 什么...
- [yells, groans]
- [喊叫，呻吟]
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
- Hey, um, Patrick?
- 嘿，嗯，帕特里克？
Could you, uh,
bump the grill temperature up
你能不能，呃，
提高烤架温度
about half a degree?
大约半度？
- Fine.
- 美好的。
- And you should be
flipping the patties
- 你应该是
翻转肉饼
with a clockwise
wrist motion because
以顺时针方向
手腕运动是因为
the customers can always
taste the difference!
客户总是可以
尝尝差别！
- [moans]
Whatever you say, boss.
- [呻吟]
老板你说什么都行。
[babbles]
[胡言乱语]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
No, Patrick!
We went over this!
不，帕特里克！
我们讨论过这个！
It goes bun, patty,
cheese, pickles,
它变成了面包，肉饼，
奶酪、泡菜、
lettuce, tomatoes, bun!
生菜，西红柿，面包！
Not bun, patty,
cheese, lettuce,
不是馒头、肉饼，
奶酪、生菜、
pickles, tomatoes, bun!
泡菜，西红柿，面包！
- That's it!
- 就是这样！
This was supposed to be fun,
这本来应该很有趣
but now it's, uh,
the other thing!
但现在是，呃，
另一件事！
I quit!
[gulp]
我不干了！
[吞咽]
These too!
还有这些！
- But Patrick,
you're my best friend-ployee!
- 但是帕特里克，
你是我最好的朋友-员工！
[rapid groaning]
[快速呻吟]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Shpoink!
Wow!
嘘！
哇！
Aren't you a real slice off
the ol' block!
你不是一个真正的切片吗
老街区！
Can you work the grill?
- Ah! Mm-hmm!
你能操作烤架吗？
- 啊！嗯嗯！
- [laughs]
You're hired.
- [笑]
你被录用了。
Ahh.
啊。
[crowd clamoring]
[人群喧闹]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- Mr. Squidward,
it's not time for your break!
- 章鱼哥先生
现在还不是你休息的时间！
- I'm taking a permanent break
from you!
- 我要永久休息
来自你！
I quit!
我不干了！
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
- No!
[whimpers]
- 不！
[呜咽]
Oh, uh-oh!
I need more employees!
哦，呃-哦！
我需要更多员工！
Ooh!
Uh, just a second everybody!
哦！
呃，大家稍等一下！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[crowd clamoring]
[人群喧闹]
- How can I help you?
- 我怎么帮你？
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的喋喋不休]
- Oh...
- Phew!
- 哦...
- 唷！
Everything's under
control now, Mr. K.
一切都在下面
现在控制一下，K先生。
I guarantee it.
我保证。
- Oh, dear!
- 哦亲爱的！
Oops!
I spilled!
哎呀！
我洒了！
- Wow!
- 哇！
Oops!
I fell down!
哎呀！
我摔倒了！
- Oh!
- 哦！
- Hey, how come
the TV don't work?
- 嘿，怎么会这样
电视不能用？
- Ooh!
Oh, no!
- 哦！
哦，不！
- It's too hot in here!
- 这里太热了！
- [yells]
- [大喊]
- It's too cold in here!
- 这里太冷了！
[wind blows]
[风吹过]
- What do I do?
- 我该怎么办？
What do I do?
我该怎么办？
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
- [strains]
- [菌株]
Everybody, stop!
大家停下来！
[pants]
[裤子]
[grinding, crowd groans]
[研磨，人群呻吟]
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [moans]
- [呻吟]
♪ ♪
- Ah!
- 啊！
- [whines]
- [哀嚎]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- Don't mind me.
- 别介意我。
I'm just here
to clean out my desk.
我就在这里
清理我的桌子。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[wind blows]
[风吹过]
- Oh, no!
My slices!
- 哦，不！
我的切片！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Stop, please!
请停下来！
You're ruining the Krusty Krab
dining experience!
你毁了蟹堡王
用餐体验！
[crowd groaning]
[人群呻吟]
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
[yells, pants]
[喊叫，裤子]
- Mr. Krabs!
You're all better!
- 蟹老板！
你们都好多了！
Sorry, I let you down.
抱歉，我让你失望了。
All I wanted was to be
a good boss, just like you.
我想要的只是成为
一个好老板，就像你一样。
- Oh, well, there's no need
-哦，好吧，没必要
to get yer sails
in a twist about it, boy.
去获得你的风帆
事情有点转折，孩子。
Nobody's just like me,
especially you!
没有人像我一样
尤其是你！
Besides, you saved me months
in that there body cast.
此外，你还帮我节省了几个月的时间
在那里有身体铸造。
If it weren't for the rage
如果不是因为愤怒
I felt watching you
destroy me restaurant,
我感觉在看着你
毁掉我餐厅，
I would ya never forced me
body to heal so quickly!
我希望你永远不会强迫我
身体恢复得这么快！
- Oh, so in a way,
I done good, huh?
- 哦，所以在某种程度上，
我做得很好吧？
- Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- 哦，不！
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Not even close.
You were the worst boss ever!
甚至还差得远。
你是有史以来最糟糕的老板！
I'm gonna have to dock
your pay for decades
我必须靠岸
你几十年的工资
just to cover all
the damage you caused.
只是为了覆盖所有
你造成的伤害。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- Oh, thanks, Mr. Krabs!
You're the best boss ever!
- 噢，谢谢蟹老板！
你是有史以来最好的老板！